Once Upon A Time In A Small Village Surrounded By Mountains
There Lived A 24 Year Old Young Man
Named Marco.
Marco Was Very Restless
His Mind Was Always Full Of Thoughts
All Day Long Different Thoughts Came And
Went
And These Thoughts Made Him Feel Uneasy
And Tired
He Always Felt Sad About His Past And Worried A Lot About The Future
Because Of These Thoughts
His Mind Was Like A Storm
He Couldn't Feel Calm, Couldn't Sleep Well
And Even Forgot How To Smile
One Day,, Marco Heard About A Far Away
Village In The Hillss
One Day, Marco Heard About A Far Away
That Man Used To Be A Famous Psychologist In The City
He Had Helped Many People In His Life
And Had Taught Them How To Find Peace In
Their Minds
4.
Now He Was Old
He Left The Busy Life Of The City
And Started Living In A Quiet Village
Close To Nature
Sometimes He Gave Advice To Visitors
Marco Became Curious And Hopeful
He Decided That He Must Go And Meet That
Old Man
He Thought.. Maybe This Wise Man Can Help
Me Find Peace
After Many Days Of A Long And Tiring
Journey
Marco Reached The Village In The Hills
When He Got There, He Saw A Small House
Covered With Greenery
ل
On The Porch Of The House The Old Man Was Sitting Quietly
His Eyes Were Closed And He Looked Very
Peaceful
Marco Walked Up To Him And Said Softly
Grandfather, My Mind Is Very Restless
I Cannot Stop Thinking I Want Peace In My
Heart
Can You Help Me?
The Old Man Slowly Opened His Eyes And
Gave A Calm Smile
He Said So You Are Looking For Peace
Then Come With Me I Will Give You A Small
Task
He Took Marco To His Little Yard
Then He Filled A Glass With Water
Completely Full To The Top
The Glass Was So Full
That Even A Little Shake Would Make The
Water Spill
He Gave The Glass To Marco And Said
Walk From Here To The Edge Of The Village And Then Come Back
But Remember You Must Not Spill Even One
Drop Of Water
Marco Looked At Him With Surprise
But He Wanted To Do His Best
So He Accepted The Challenge
He Held The Glass Carefully And Started
Walking
The Road Was Narrow And Busy
Some People Were Walking Some Were
n
Running
Shopkeepers Were Calling Customers And
Dogs Were Barking
But Marco Did Not Look Around
His Eyes Stayed Only On The Glass
He Walked Slowly And Carefully
Step By Step
People Looked At Him With Surprise
But No One Disturbed Him They Knew He Was Learning Something Important
Finally Marco Came Back To The Old Mar
And Said
Grandfather I Did It
I Didn't Spill Even One Drop Of Water
4ŷ
ز مرید کرده
The Old Man Nodded And Smiled
'?
Then He Asked That's Good
But Tell Me Did You See The Children Playing
On The Side Of The Road
Did You Hear The Dogs Barking
ވ
Marco Looked Surprised And Said No
I Didn't See Or Hear Anything
I Was Only Focusing On The Glass
The Old Man Smiled Again And Said Gently
That Is The Secret
Something That Was Always Inside You But
You Didn't Know
When Your Mind Stays In The Present
Moment
Then There Is No Space For Fear
No Confusion And No Extra Thoughts
You Were Only Thinking About The Water In
The Glass
At That Time Your Mind Became Completely
Quiet
You Were Not Sad About The Past
You Were Not Afraid Of The Future
Slowly
Marco Began To Understand This Was The
Peace He Was Searching For
Peace Is Not Something We Find Outside
Peace Is Already Inside Us When We Live In
The Present Moment
Marco Bowed His Head And Said Softly
Grandfather Now I Understand
If I Want To Calm My Mind
I Must Keep My Mind In This Moment
That Is When Real Peace Comes
The Old Man Smiled Again
The Sun Was Setting And The Last Light
Touched The Ground
Birds Were Flying Back To Their Nests
Marco Started Walking Back Home
But Now He Was Not The Same Restless
Young Man
He Had Changed
He Was Peaceful Inside Because Now He
Knew How To Calm The Mind